let questions=[
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which Australian state is known for its capital city, Sydney, famous for its iconic Opera House and Harbour Bridge?",
        answer: "B. New South Wales",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which state is home to the Great Barrier Reef, one of the world's most extensive coral reef systems?",
        answer: "D. Queensland",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Cradle Mountain is a popular tourist destination located in which Australian state?",
        answer: "C. Tasmania",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The Gold Coast, famous for its beautiful beaches and theme parks, is located in which state?",
        answer: "D. Queensland",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Port Arthur Historic Site, a former convict settlement, can be found in which state?",
        answer: "C. Tasmania",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The Great Ocean Road, a scenic coastal drive, is a major attraction in which state?",
        answer: "A. Victoria",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which state is known for its stunning landscapes, including Freycinet National Park and Wineglass Bay?",
        answer: "C. Tasmania",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "The Whitsunday Islands, a popular destination for sailing and snorkeling, are located in which state?",
        answer: "D. Queensland",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The Blue Mountains, known for their scenic beauty and hiking trails, are located in which state?",
        answer: "B. New South Wales",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The capital city of Melbourne is located in which Australian state?",
        answer: "A. Victoria",
        Option: [   "A. Victoria",
                    "B. New South Wales",
                    "C. Tasmania",
                    "D. Queensland",
            
        ]
    },
];